Guide to the Ralph W. Cummings Papers
Ralph W. Cummings Papers
- Professional Papers, 1952-1997; 1952 1997; 33.5 linear feet
  - Research and Related Materials, 1952-1997
    - International Assistance for Strengthening National Agricultural Research (ISNAR) (2 of 4), 1974-1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - International Assistance for Strengthening National Agricultural Research (ISNAR) (3 of 4), 1974-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - International Assistance for Strengthening National Agricultural Research (ISNAR) (4 of 4), 1974-1981 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - International Rice Research Institute, 1975-1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Jamaica Mission, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Japan Tsokuba Seminar, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Development Council, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Agricultural Development Council Information Systems Seminar, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Asian Development Bank, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Asian Association of Agricultural Colleges and Universities (AAACU) Newsletters, 1977-1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Biology Identification and Control of Root-knot Nematodes, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - NCSU Blue Bulletins, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Ecuador- Background Information for Development Projects, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Hawaii Resource Systems Institute - East West Center, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - India Development Service (IDS), 1977-1978? (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - International Foundation for Science, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - India Agricultural Research Institute (IARI), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - India Agricultural Research Institute (IARI), 1964 - 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - India Research League of America, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - The Land Institute, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - United States Department of Agriculture, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Land Tenure Center Newsletters, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - MacArthur Foundation (1 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - MacArthur Foundation (2 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - MacArthur Foundation (3 of 3), 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Marcus Wallberg Prize, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - IADS Nepal Assignment, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Ohio State Agronomy Newsletter, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Research Foundation Ohio State University Board of Directors, 1968-1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR Tac Study on Plant Nutrition (1 of 2), 1981-198? (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR Tac Study on Plant Nutrition (2 of 2), 1981-198? (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Plan Puebla Mexico, 1967-1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR Statement on Plant Breeders Rights, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR Priorities for International Support to Agricultural Research in Developing Countries (1 of 2), 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR Priorities for International Support to Agricultural Research in Developing Countries (2 of 2), 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina Agriculture Experiment Station Research Administration Search for Assistant Director, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Upland Rice (1 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Upland Rice (2 of 2), 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Publication (1 of 2), 1913-1987 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Publication (2 of 2), 1913-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Correspondence (1 of 2), 1975-1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Correspondence (2 of 2), 1975-1979 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Rotary Foundation of Rotary International, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Rotary Foundation International Peace Scholarships, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Rotary Foundation Freedom from Hunger Scholarships, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Rotary International 3H Projects Famine Relief and Water Resources in Ethiopia, 1986-1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Rotary Foundation Printed Materials, 1980-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Rotary Foundation Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Rotary Foundation Correspondence, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Rotary International Annual Convention Paris, France (1 of 2), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Rotary International Annual Convention Paris, France (2 of 2), 1953 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Rotary Volunteers, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Rotary Club of Raleigh, North Carolina, 1984-1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Rotary Chapters, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Rotary International Ecuador Agricultural Training, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Rotary International Ethiopia (1 of 2), 1980-1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Rotary International Ethiopia (2 of 2), 1980-1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Shastri memorial lecture, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - International Soybean Institute, 1980? (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Dr. Leslie Swindale honorary degree, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rotary Club of Raleigh (1 of 2), 1951-1953 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Rotary Club of Raleigh (2 of 2), 1951-1953 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Rotary Club Committee Plan Handbook "Mr. President This Is Your Year', 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Rotary Club of Raleigh meeting minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - CGIAR TAC secretariat 29 July, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR TAC 23rd Meeting Manila 30 October, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR TAC 24th Meeting (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC 24th Meeting (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC 25th Meeting, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting/ secretariats 1-10, 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 13, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 14, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 14, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 15, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 16, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 17 (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 17 (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC meeting 19, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC Summations (1 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC Summations (2 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC Stripe Analysis of the Off-Campus Activities of the International agricultural Research Center, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR TAC Role and Working Procedures, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Furtick, William R. - Taro Problems and Potentials, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Turkey-Wheat Research Proposal Rockefeller Center, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Vegetable research, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Ohio State University Research Foundation, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - American Society of Agronomy (1 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - American Society of Agronomy (2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - American Chemical Society, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Alpha Zeta Alumni, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Ford Foundation, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - WARDA Quinquennial review, 1977-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - WARDA, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - ICRAF 10th Anniversary Program (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ICRAF 10th Anniversary Program (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ISNAR Board of Trustees 1st Meeting, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ICRAF Board manual, 1989-1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - IIMI 8th Internal Program (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - IIMI 8th Internal Program (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - ICRISAT Housing, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - "India Folder", 1968 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - ICRISAT correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - ICRISAT agenda notes, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Visit to South Korea - Rice and Wheat production notes and draft, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Foundation correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Indonesia-travels and discussion with joint team IRRI and Ford Foundation, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - IMMI System wide initiative for water management, 1988-1998? (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - IMMI Governing Board correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - IMMI Governing Board meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - IMMI Governing Board meeting minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - India, 1966-1968 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - CGIAR 18th TAC meeting, Rome (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR 18th TAC meeting, Rome (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR TAC 17th meeting/ quinquennial review (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR TAC 17th meeting/ quinquennial review (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR TAC 20th meeting (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC 20th meeting (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Water Buffalo research (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Water Buffalo research (2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - World Bank correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - World Bank travel expense records, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - World Bank professional service accounts, 1984-1987 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - World Bank communication secretarial, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - World Bank consultancy appointments, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Winged Bean (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Winged Bean (2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Mayaguez Institute of Tropical Agriculture (MITA) trip report, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - North Carolina State University correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - North Carolina State University correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - North Carolina State University Sea Grant College Program, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - North Carolina State University Patent Policy, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - North Carolina State University directory, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC appointment, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - emeritus professorship, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - India trip correspondence, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Rotary Club correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - CGIAR TAC chairmanship, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - CGIAR TAC membership (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - CGIAR TAC membership (2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Asian Institute for Rural Development correspondence, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Asian Institute for Rural Development publications, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - memorandum for record of telephone conversation with Reed Hertford, the Ford Foundation, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Marquis "Who's Who in the South and Southwest" application, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Development assistance committee, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - World Bank West Africa Research Review (1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - World Bank West Africa Research Review (2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - West Africa Agricultural Research Study by Burton E. Swanson and Wade H Reeves (1 of 2), 1985 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - West Africa Agricultural Research Study by Burton E. Swanson and Wade H Reeves (2 of 2), 1985 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume II Summaries of National Reports, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Cape Verde, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Chad, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III The Gambia, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Mali, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Mauritania, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Niger, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III Upper Volta, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Institut du Sahel (Sahel Institute) Assessment of Agricultural Research in the Sahel Volume III The Senegal, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - West Africa Research Review (WARR) peer review correspondence (1 of 4), 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - West Africa Research Review (WARR) peer review correspondence (2 of 4), 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - West Africa Research Review (WARR) peer review correspondence (3 of 4), 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - West Africa Research Review (WARR) peer review correspondence (4 of 4), 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR TAC review of priorities and future strategies, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - CGIAR TAC priorities for international support to agricultural research in developing countries, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - CGIAR TAC priorities for international support to agricultural research in developing countries, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Assessment of Agricultural Research Resources in the Sahel VI, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - West Africa forestry research (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - West Africa forestry research (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - World Bank Study Agricultural Research for West Africa (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - World Bank Study Agricultural Research for West Africa (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - World Bank Study Agricultural Research for West Africa (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Plan for Supporting Agricultural Research and Faculties of Agriculture in West Africa - draft for discussion, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Senegal Agricultural Research Project 5th Mission, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Impact of Agricultural Research in tropical Africa by H. E. Jahnke, D. Kirschke and j Lageman, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - World Bank Review Report C. Fred Bentley 1 of 2, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - World Bank Review Report C. Fred Bentley 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - "Agricultural Research in the West-African Coastal Zone" - German report, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - West Africa - Status of Research and Technology" presentation visuals and notes, 1983?-1986? (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - World Bank WAARR Livestock Research, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - World Bank WAARR Livestock Research, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Report on national Agricultural Research in West Africa by Peter Oram, IFPRI, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - World Bank Contonov Workshop Program Notes with Bel Abbai, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - West Africa Agriculture Research Review (WAARR) Chapter 6 Historical Perspectives, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - West Africa Bellagio conference, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - WAARR Anglophone Sahel Countries, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - WAARR Francophone Coastal Countries, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Nigeria National Programs, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Sierra Leone Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Ghana National Program, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Zaire Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Togo Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Ivory Coast Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Guinea Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Benin Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Congo Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Cameroon Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Liberia Country Report, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - International Council for Research in Agroforestry - background papers (1 of 3), 1979-1984 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - International Council for Research in Agroforestry - background papers (2 of 3), 1979-1984 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - International Council for Research in Agroforestry - background papers (3 of 3), 1979-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - WAARR Anglophone Countries Report by Leonard Shebeski and Cooenraad ter Kuile (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - WAARR Anglophone Countries Report by Leonard Shebeski and Cooenraad ter Kuile (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Tree Crops Institute - proposal draft by John F Greenwood, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - WAARR Chapter 6 Section C - Tree Crops revised, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - West African Livestock - preliminary on strategy by R.E. McDowell, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - West African Research Review Appendices, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - National Agricultural Research West Africa Sahelian Countries, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - WAARR Chapter 6 Section E Livestock - draft, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Forestry Research in Eastern and Southern Africa - report to World Bank, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - WAARR draft review comments by Howard Elliot, [1986?] (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - ISNAR - - Special Program for African Agricultural Research (SPAARS) guidelines for strengthening National Agriculture Research Systems (NARS) - draft, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Tree Crops - Ollinger Report, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - National Agricultural Research West Africa Coastal Francophone Countries by Francis Lebeau and Miles Wedeman (1 of 2), [1985?] (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - National Agricultural Research West Africa Coastal Francophone Countries by Francis Lebeau and Miles Wedeman (2 of 2), [1985?] (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - WAARR Full Report for review at Cotonou Workshop (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - WAARR Full Report for review at Cotonou Workshop (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - WAARR Full Report for review at Cotonou Workshop (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - African Swine Fever (1 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - African Swine Fever (2 of 2), 1978-1980 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Agricultural Water Resources, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - American Society of Agronomy, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Animal Agriculture Symposium, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Asian Agricultural Universities, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Asian Development Bank, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Asian Institute for Rural Development (AID) (1 of 2), 1948-1994 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Asian Institute for Rural Development (AID) (2 of 2), 1948-1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - King Baudouin International Development Prize to the CGIAR, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Cassava, 1976-1979 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - CGIAR (1 of 2), 1979-1985 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - CGIAR (1 of 2), 1979-1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - China Agricultural Research Institute, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - New Delhi Union Church, 1962-1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - International Potato Center - Lima, Peru, 1976-1980 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Farmers Welfare Trust Dinner, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Ford Foundation, 1966-1991 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Ford Foundation correspondence, 1971-1983 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Wayne H (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Freeman, Wayne H (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Farming Systems, 1976-1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Gamma Alphan - fraternity newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Plant Genetic Resources, 1977-1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - International Agriculture Development Systems, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - International Board for Plant Genetic Resources, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Conferences and Symposia - International Conference Bellagio, Italy, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Conferences and Symposia - Canada and world Food - Ottowa, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Conferences and Symposia - CRIA Maros, South Sulawesi, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Conferences and Symposia - 6th International Cereal and bread Congress, Winnipeg, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Conferences and Symposia - "The Role of International Studies: The University and the Community" NCSU Faculty Club, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Conferences and Symposia -Pullman Kellogg Ammonia Client Meeting, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Conferences and Symposia - Adaptive Production Systems Meeting - The East West Center, Honolulu, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - International Board for Soil Research Management (IBSRM) 1 of 2, 1979-1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - International Board for Soil Research Management (IBSRM) 2 of 2, 1979-1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - International Board for Plant Genetic Resources, 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - International Center for Mountain Development (1 of 2), 1982--1987 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - International Center for Mountain Development (2 of 2), 1982--1987 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology (1 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - International Center of Insect Physiology and Ecology (2 of 2), 1977-1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - International Council for Research Agroforestry, [1982?] (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - International Crops Research Institute (ICRISAT), 1978-1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - International Food Policy Research Institute (1 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - International Food Policy Research Institute (2 of 2), 1977-1981 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1979-1981 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - International Irrigation Management Institute (IIMI) Agreements (1 of 2), 1972-1983 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - International Irrigation Management Institute (IIMI) Agreements (2 of 2), 1972-1983 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - IIMI Budgets, 1981-1986 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - IIMI Computers, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - IIMI Liaisons for office prospects, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - IIMI Employment, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - IIMI Funding, 1982-1984 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - IIMI Headquarters New Kandy Sri Lanka (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - IIMI Headquarters New Kandy Sri Lanka (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - IIMI Legal Counsel, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD) Nairobi, Kenya (1 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD) Nairobi, Kenya (2 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases (ILRAD) Nairobi, Kenya (3 of 3), 1979-1982 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - ILRAD Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - International Livestock Center for Africa (ILCA), 1979-1981 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - CGIAR Integrative Reports (1 of 3), 1976-1981 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - CGIAR Integrative Reports (2 of 3), 1976-1981 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - CGIAR Integrative Reports (3 of 3), 1976-1981 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - CGIAR Quinquennial Reviews (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - CGIAR Quinquennial Reviews (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - CGIAR Quinquennial Reviews (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - West African Tree Crops Research - draft (1 of 4), 1986 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - West African Tree Crops Research - draft (2 of 4), 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - West African Tree Crops Research - draft (3 of 4), 1986 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - West African Tree Crops Research - draft (4 of 4), 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - WAAR - working group memos and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - WAAR - workshop materials and notes, 1984-1986 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - WAAR - workshop Conotou Agreements, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - WAAR - workshop Conotou Funding and Budgets, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 1)